const cards = [
     [
        {
            front: 'eple',
            back: 'apple'
        },
        {
            front: 'melk',
            back: 'milk'
        },
        {
            front: 'brød',
            back: 'bread'
        },
        {
            front: 'kjøtt',
            back: 'meat'
        },
        {
            front: 'grønnsaker',
            back: 'vegetables'
        },
        {
            front: 'fisk',
            back: 'fish'
        },
        {
            front: 'is',
            back: 'ice-cream'
        },
        {
            front: 'syltetøy',
            back: 'jam'
        },
        {
            front: 'vann',
            back: 'water'
        },
        {
            front: 'sjokolade',
            back: 'chocolate'
        },
        {
            front: 'pølse',
            back: 'sausage'
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            front: 'sokk',
            back: 'sock'
        },
        {
            front: 'sko',
            back: 'shoe'
        },
        {
            front: 'genser',
            back: 'jumper'
        },
        {
            front: 'lue',
            back: 'hat'
        },
        {
            front: 'slips',
            back: 'tie'
        },
        {
            front: 'støvel',
            back: 'boot'
        },
        {
            front: 'shorts',
            back: 'shorts'
        },
        {
            front: 'T-skjorte',
            back: 't-shirt'
        },
        {
            front: 'kjole',
            back: 'dress'
        },
        {
            front: 'jakke',
            back: 'jacket'
        },
        {
            front: 'bukse',
            back: 'trousers'
        }
    ],
     [
        {
            front: 'gul',
            back: 'yellow'
        },
        {
            front: 'oransje',
            back: 'orange'
        },
        {
            front: 'hvit',
            back: 'white'
        },
        {
            front: 'grønn',
            back: 'green'
        },
        {
            front: 'blå',
            back: 'blue'
        },
        {
            front: 'rosa',
            back: 'pink'
        },
        {
            front: 'rød',
            back: 'red'
        },
        {
            front: 'svart',
            back: 'black'
        },
        {
            front: 'brun',
            back: 'brown'
        },
        {
            front: 'grå',
            back: 'grey'
        },
        {
            front: 'lilla',
            back: 'purple'
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            front: 'pute',
            back: 'pillow'
        },
        {
            front: 'hylle',
            back: 'shelf'
        },
        {
            front: 'sofa',
            back: 'sofa'
        },
        {
            front: 'bord',
            back: 'table'
        },
        {
            front: 'seng',
            back: 'bed'
        },
        {
            front: 'kjøleskap',
            back: 'fridge'
        },
        {
            front: 'benk',
            back: 'bench'
        },
        {
            front: 'stol',
            back: 'chair'
        },
        {
            front: 'badekar',
            back: 'bathtub'
        },
        {
            front: 'garderobe',
            back: 'wardrobe'
        },
        {
            front: 'skuff',
            back: 'drawer'
        }
    ]
];
